<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Learn Android</string>

    <string name="about_auther_string">
        Proffession : Student\nUniversity  : Primeasia University\nSubject     : Computer Science and Engineering\nEmail       : saiful161003@gmail.com\nReligion    : Islam\nAge         : 23\n</string>

    <string-array name="content_list">
        <item>Common UI Widgets</item>
        <item>Intent</item>
        <item>Containers</item>
        <item>Menu</item>
        <item>Date Time</item>
        <item>Animation</item>
        <item>Aoudio</item>
        <item>Video</item>
        <item>Camera</item>
        <item>Fragment</item>
        <item>Map</item>
        <item>SQlite</item>
        <item>Toast</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="common_widget_list">
        <item>TextView</item>
        <item>EditText</item>
        <item>Button</item>
        <item>ImageButton</item>
        <item>Switch</item>
        <item>CheckBox</item>
        <item>AlertDialog</item>
        <item>ScrollView</item>
        <item>ProgressBar</item>
        <item>Seekbar</item>
        <item>RadioButton</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="common_widget">Common Widget</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="java">Java</string>
    <string name="xml">XML</string>
    <string name="manifest">Manifest</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>

    <string name="alert_title"> Alert</string>
    <string name="alert_msg">Do you want to exit?</string>


    <string name="textview_description">TextView is a user interface element that displays text to the user.\n\nIt used to show text to the user.</string>
    <string name="edittext_description">A user interface element for entering and modifying text.\n\nIt used to read Text from user.</string>
    <string name="button_description">A Button is a user interface element the user can tap or click to perform an action.</string>
    <string name="image_button_description">Displays a button with an image (instead of text) that can be pressed or clicked by the user. By default,
        an ImageButton looks like a regular Button, with the standard button background that changes color during different button states.</string>
    <string name="switch_description">A Switch is a two-state toggle switch widget that can select between two options. The user may drag the "thumb"
        back and forth to choose the selected option, or simply tap to toggle as if it were a checkbox. The text property controls the text displayed
        in the label for the switch, whereas the off and on text controls the text on the thumb.</string>
    <string name="check_box_description">A checkbox is a specific type of two-states button that can be either checked or unchecked.</string>
    <string name="alert_dialog_description">A dialog that can show a title, up to three buttons, a list of selectable items, or a custom layout.</string>
    <string name="scroll_view_description">A view group that allows the view hierarchy placed within it to be scrolled. Scroll view may have only one
        direct child placed within it. To add multiple views within the scroll view, make the direct child you add a view group, for example LinearLayout,
        and place additional views within that LinearLayout.Scroll view supports vertical scrolling only. For horizontal scrolling, use HorizontalScrollView instead.</string>
    <string name="prgressbar_description">A user interface element that indicates the progress of an operation. Progress bar supports two modes to represent progress:
        determinate, and indeterminate.Show the progress bar in your apps user interface or in a notification instead of within a dialog.</string>
    <string name="seekbar_description">A SeekBar is an extension of ProgressBar that adds a draggable thumb. The user can touch the thumb and drag
        left or right to set the current progress level or use the arrow keys. Placing focusable widgets to the left or right of a SeekBar is discouraged.</string>
    <string name="radiobutton_description">Radio buttons allow the user to select one option from a set. You should use radio buttons for optional sets that are
        mutually exclusive if you think that the user needs to see all available options side-by-side. If its not necessary to show all options side-by-side, use a spinner instead.</string>
    <string name="toast_description">A toast provides simple feedback about an operation in a small popup. It only fills the amount of space required for the message and the current activity
        remains visible and interactive. Toasts automatically disappear after a timeout.</string>
    <string name="sample8"></string>
    <string name="sample9"></string>
    <string name="sample10"></string>
    <string name="sample11"></string>
    <string name="sample12"></string>
    <string name="sample14"></string>
    <string name="sample13"></string>
    <string name="sample15"></string>
    <string name="sample17"></string>
    <string name="sample16"></string>
    <string name="sample27"></string>

</resources>
