<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Learn Android</string>

    <string name="about_auther_string">
        Proffession : Student\nUniversity  : Primeasia University\nSubject     : Computer Science and Engineering\nEmail       : saiful161003@gmail.com\nReligion    : Islam\nAge         : 23\n</string>

    <string-array name="content_list">
        <item>Common UI Widgets</item>
        <item>Intent</item>
        <item>Containers</item>
        <item>Menu</item>
        <item>Date Time</item>
        <item>Animation</item>
        <item>Aoudio</item>
        <item>Video</item>
        <item>Camera</item>
        <item>Fragment</item>
        <item>Map</item>
        <item>SQlite</item>
        <item>Toast</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="common_widget_list">
        <item>TextView</item>
        <item>EditText</item>
        <item>Button</item>
        <item>ImageButton</item>
        <item>Switch</item>
        <item>CheckBox</item>
        <item>AlertDialog</item>
        <item>ScrollView</item>
        <item>ProgressBar</item>
        <item>Seekbar</item>
        <item>RadioButton</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="common_widget">Common Widget</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="java">Java</string>
    <string name="xml">XML</string>
    <string name="manifest">Manifest</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>

    <string name="alert_title"> Alert</string>
    <string name="alert_msg">Do you want to exit?</string>


    <string name="textview_description">TextView is a user interface element that displays text to the user.\n\nIt used to show text to the user.</string>
    <string name="edittext_description">A user interface element for entering and modifying text.\n\nIt used to read Text from user.</string>
    <string name="button_description">A Button is a user interface element the user can tap or click to perform an action.</string>
    <string name="image_button_description">Displays a button with an image (instead of text) that can be pressed or clicked by the user. By default,
        an ImageButton looks like a regular Button, with the standard button background that changes color during different button states.</string>
    <string name="switch_description">A Switch is a two-state toggle switch widget that can select between two options. The user may drag the "thumb"
        back and forth to choose the selected option, or simply tap to toggle as if it were a checkbox. The text property controls the text displayed
        in the label for the switch, whereas the off and on text controls the text on the thumb.</string>
    <string name="check_box_description">A checkbox is a specific type of two-states button that can be either checked or unchecked.</string>
    <string name="alert_dialog_description">A dialog that can show a title, up to three buttons, a list of selectable items, or a custom layout.</string>
    <string name="scroll_view_description">A view group that allows the view hierarchy placed within it to be scrolled. Scroll view may have only one
        direct child placed within it. To add multiple views within the scroll view, make the direct child you add a view group, for example LinearLayout,
        and place additional views within that LinearLayout.Scroll view supports vertical scrolling only. For horizontal scrolling, use HorizontalScrollView instead.</string>
    <string name="prgressbar_description">A user interface element that indicates the progress of an operation. Progress bar supports two modes to represent progress:
        determinate, and indeterminate.Show the progress bar in your apps user interface or in a notification instead of within a dialog.</string>
    <string name="seekbar_description">A SeekBar is an extension of ProgressBar that adds a draggable thumb. The user can touch the thumb and drag
        left or right to set the current progress level or use the arrow keys. Placing focusable widgets to the left or right of a SeekBar is discouraged.</string>
    <string name="radiobutton_description">Radio buttons allow the user to select one option from a set. You should use radio buttons for optional sets that are
        mutually exclusive if you think that the user needs to see all available options side-by-side. If its not necessary to show all options side-by-side,
        use a spinner instead.</string>
    <string name="toast_description">A toast provides simple feedback about an operation in a small popup. It only fills the amount of space required for the
        message and the current activity
        remains visible and interactive. Toasts automatically disappear after a timeout.</string>
    <string name="SQLite_description">SQLite is a opensource SQL database that stores data to a text file on a device. Android comes in
        with built in SQLite database implementation.SQLite supports all the relational database features. In order to access this database,
        you dont need to establish any kind of connections for it like JDBC,ODBC e.t.c</string>
    <string name="timePicker_description">A widget for selecting the time of day, in either 24-hour or AM/PM mode.</string>
    <string name="clock_description">A clock providing access to the current instant, date and time using a time-zone.</string>
    <string name="animation_description">Animations can add visual cues that notify users about whats going on in your app. They are especially
        useful when the UI changes state, such as when new content loads or new actions become available. Animations also add a polished look to
        your app, which gives it a higher quality look and feel.Android includes different animation APIs depending on what type of animation you want</string>
    <string name="listview_description">Android ListView is a view which groups several items and display them in vertical scrollable list. The list items
        are automatically inserted to the list using an Adapter that pulls content from a source such as an array or database.</string>
    <string name="recyclerview_description">RecyclerView is a ViewGroup added to the android studio as a successor of the GridView and
        ListView. It is an improvement on both of them and can be found in the latest v-7 support packages. It has been created to make
        possible construction of any lists with XML layouts as an item which can be customized vastly while improving on the efficiency
        of ListViews and GridViews.</string>
    <string name="option_menu_description">The options menu is the primary collection of menu items for an activity.
        Its where you should place actions that have a global impact on the app, such as "Search," "Compose email," and "Settings."</string>
    <string name="contextmenu_description">A context menu is a floating menu that appears when the user performs a long-click on an element.
        It provides actions that affect the selected content or context fra</string>
    <string name="popupmenu_description">A popup menu displays a list of items in a vertical list thats anchored to the view that invoked the\
        menu. It is good for providing an overflow of actions that relate to specific content or to provide options for a second part of a command.</string>
    <string name="explicitintent_description">Android Explicit intent specifies the component to be invoked from activity. In other words, we can call another
        activity in android by explicit intent.We can also pass the information from one activity to another using explicit intent.</string>
    <string name="implicitintent_description">Implicit intents do not name a specific component, but instead declare a general action to perform,
        which allows a component from another app to handle it. For example, if you want to show the user a location on a map, you can use an 
        implicit intent to request that another capable app show a specified location on a map.</string>
    <string name="sample18"></string>
    <string name="sample19"></string>
    <string name="sample20"></string>
    <string name="sample21"></string>

</resources>
